Who are you?
Are you
Bella Jin?
Wait, but I thought you were in Barcelona.
I got a call
that someone was looking for me.
You must be the ace.
Me? Yes.
Anyway, I'm Bella Jin.
I'm Seo Ji-woo, Director of JARIM Apparel.
Let me first pay for the scarf…
I'm afraid you can't.
Ji-woo.
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
The ace here grabbed that scarf first.
I did grab it first, but sure, go ahead.
It's only right for us to buy it.
Hey, this one. Isn't this pretty? No?
You have the Delta two-piece?
Yes.
My mom does.
Oh, hey.
Okay. Here.
Gracias.
EPISODE 9
I get the situation.
Actually, when I got the call
that you wanted to see me…
The call was
from Trend D's editor-in-chief.
I looked up JARIM Apparel.
And Daniel knows you, Ms. Seo Ji-woo.
I asked him just in case. You know Daniel?
Yes. My friend in England.
He runs a select shop.
Daniel said I should meet you.
I appreciate that you came
all the way here.
I think I already know what this is about.
But I have nothing to discuss with you.
But since we've had coffee,
is that enough for the greeting?
You're right. We've come a long way.
Will you spare your time for Director Seo
to explain? We'd appreciate it.
Is the scarf for your mom?
You're not on good terms
with your mom, are you?
Can you tell?
It'll be a good gift.
Málaga is nice. You might as well
check it out while you're here.
It was actually nice meeting you.
I'll root for JARIM Apparel. Bye now.
But, Bella. I…
Hey, let's follow her.
Wait.
We need a strategy.
You said we needed a strategy.
Waiting is also a strategy.
Let's get up there and ring the doorbell.
We can't just wait here forever.
Isn't she having dinner?
She'd come down soon.
Hey!
Have you been waiting here?
It's a nice alley. I like watching alleys.
We've been waiting for a very long time.
My legs are swollen, and I'm hungry.
Do you like wine?
What about you? You don't drink?
I'm… taking oriental medicine.
I should refrain from alcohol,
flour, or anything spicy…
Ji-woo, is he your ace?
Sorry?
I've read your article. You two met
while doing theater together or something?
Anyway,
you two met when you were 20,
and it didn't end.
The ace wrote about your ex-husband?
I didn't publish it myself,
but technically, it was me. Yes.
You two are not in love.
There's a word for it.
"Baseless." Is it really baseless?
Yes, that's correct. Baseless.
What about now?
Now we're together.
Well… to continue on with my explanation…
You met when you were 20,
and you're still in love?
Have you ever liked any other woman?
Am I too indiscreet?
Well…
I am kind of flustered. Yes.
I need the answer.
I have.
The 28-year-old Seo Ji-woo.
You're a selfish guy.
What?
He is?
You grew old, from 20 to 28,
all the while loving her,
and not taking your eyes off her.
And even now,
you came all the way here for Seo Ji-woo,
but how come you don't respect my love?
Yes.
I get that Pirco to you
is what Seo Ji-woo is to Lee Kyeong-do.
Thanks.
All right.
This is where our conversation begins.
Who's going to be Lucas's successor?
Judy Wong or me?
Judy Wong.
On what grounds?
After Pirco's oldest son took over,
trouble brewed between him and Lucas.
They were going in different directions.
He is likely to choose Judy Wong
rather than Lucas' protégé, Bella Jin.
It's not that he's likely to choose her,
but it's already been decided.
Why did I go to Barcelona?
I went to see it for myself.
Pirco's owner was coming to Barcelona,
and I heard the rumor
that Judy Wong was accompanying him.
If they went there together,
hundred percent.
Then you're...
not coming to JARIM, are you?
No, I'm not leaving Pirco.
You should put it that way.
Even if I get to work under Judy Wong,
I have to accept it.
It was decided in my dad's laundromat
when I was 15.
I can still draw that dress from Pirco
even with my eyes closed.
It is what it is.
There's no other way.
Let me say goodbye before I get drunk.
Thank you for coming all the way here.
Thanks to you two, I'm less angry.
It was a good idea
to exercise regularly, right?
I mean, you jog a lot, don't you?
Gosh…
I'll tell everything to Mommy.
Hang in there a little more.
Just a little more, Kyeong-do.
CAUTION
ELEVATOR OUT OF ORDER
Oh, no. Are you crying? Are those tears?
Is this funny?
No.
You can carry her too.
You can carry her up to the 2nd floor.
Oh, stop talking. Hurry up.
This is so narrow.
Gosh, are you okay?
Gosh. Shit.
Damn it.
Shit. Shit.
Good job.
We did well.
We were polite.
With respect and honor, we let her go.
That was cool.
But we came all the way here.
You used so many of your vacation days.
That was your first step as a director.
So it's a bummer.
I tried to take it for granted.
I'm going to take it slowly from scratch.
I'll find good designers so we can be
on the Paris and New York runways.
Just thinking about it
makes my stomach ticklish.
Why does your stomach get ticklish
when you have happy thoughts?
-You remember that?
-Hey, what was that for?
You still have strength left?
You definitely could have carried her.
Seo Ji-woo, don't move.
Don't be like this. I'm hungry.
-Engage your spine.
-No…
-Be ready.
-But…
-All right.
-No, I…
Walk to the runway like this. Okay?
Hey, come down. You'll break my backbone.
CEO Seo.
She's keeping it a secret and fighting it.
But the truth is, she's getting worse.
How could I not know when I'm watching her
so closely? It's kind of pitiful.
Don't mind Seo Ji-woo's word
on getting rid of MANZAAR.
You've seen it too.
Getting rid of MANZAAR,
that's her first mission? My goodness.
Isn't that brilliant and bold?
Executive Director Choi.
When Seo Ji-woo returns from Spain,
she'll soon look ridiculous.
How is she going to scout
a luxury brand designer?
She probably went because she had a plan.
Do you trust her?
Not yet.
That's what I mean.
Still, I'm looking forward to it.
She might not sell the company
for a dirt cheap price.
I'm getting the thought
that Seo Ji-woo could be the dark horse.
Executive Director Choi.
Can't you feel it?
The atmosphere is brightening up.
Young employees are supporting Seo Ji-woo.
Director Seo Ji-woo said
she'd bring a luxury brand designer
who lives up to their name.
You think she brightened up the mood
without any plans?
Seriously?
Right now, I'm even thinking
that JARIM's second prime is coming.
What if she fails
to bring a designer?
Then Seo Ji-woo
will turn out to be digging her own grave.
Here.
Do you want milk?
Kyeong-do.
Yes?
Move your damn head.
You're blocking the tiny sea view we have.
-Happy now?
-Yes. Nice.
Yes. Good job.
I wonder if Bella Jin is okay.
We should say goodbye before we go.
Should I call her?
JOIN ME TO RELIEVE YOUR HANGOVER?
She wants to relieve a hangover together.
Lucas's number.
I was wasted last night.
I was struck by the Delta two-piece
and by the Seo Ji-woo and Pirco metaphor.
I got so excited that I talked to Lucas
on the phone for an hour.
He hasn't decided where to go.
I recommended you
under the influence of wine.
Thank you for carrying me
to the 5th floor.
He said it's interesting
that you spotted the Delta scarf
at a street stall in Málaga.
By interesting, he means…
When Lucas likes a result,
he calls it interesting.
Call him.
He wouldn't give you an immediate answer,
but give him time.
Interesting…
You know, every country
has different alleys. I like it here too.
What's your favorite?
The alley next to Somang Laundromat?
Oh, right. Let's buy snacks.
Why? Are you hungry?
No, not that.
Something you'd find
in the department store.
Pretty and delicious.
Department store…
Pretty and delicious?
Not from a real one,
but if we could find something like that.
Then… a dessert?
LETTER OF INTENT TO SUE
JARIM DIRECTOR KANG MIN-WOO
Hey, CEO Bae.
You scared me. Is this really necessary?
If this doesn't get resolved,
I'm going to talk to CEO Seo Ji-yeon.
No!
We're almost there.
If you do this, we'll both--
I heard Seo Ji-woo went to Spain.
She's working hard.
If it's like this, I can't vouch for you.
Sorry. I'm still in a meeting.
ACCUSED
KANG MIN-WOO
What are you going to do about this?
Hello.
Oh, hello. One second, okay?
-Hey, look.
-Yes.
I asked to remove the stain, not smear it.
How am I supposed to wear this?
That's why I explained it to you
in the first place.
It's not easy to remove the red oil stain.
I also explained to you
that a dark fabric could be bleached.
"Could" means there was a way
to prevent it, no?
Because you kept the stain for too long,
it wasn't easy to remove.
Then you should've said
you couldn't do it.
This is my favorite dress.
Damn it.
You must've really liked it.
Who are you to barge in?
Sorry.
What do you want me to do?
Why are you asking me?
That's what I need to know.
Are you going to get me the same dress?
You won't be able to find the same one.
That's too old,
so you can't even find it in the outlets.
Hey, who are you to keep barging in?
Well, it's just an unfortunate situation…
Then mind your own business and walk away.
Wait, this is from JARIM Apparel.
Isn't it?
You got nothing else to do?
You think this is funny?
I do have other things to do.
And so do they. It seems you're the one
with nothing else to do.
I'll call the police.
Are you out of your mind?
Take this and get whatever dress you want
from our store.
JARIM
SEO JI-WOO
Which store is the closest?
I'll let them know.
The closest store… I'll have to look.
Can I really take whatever I want?
Yes.
Even the Lusae store in Cheongdam-dong?
Yes, I'll call them.
Wait, you need to pay before you go.
What?
For removing the stain and dry cleaning.
Wait.
Don't forget to take this.
Your favorite dress.
Well…
Here. I didn't buy it
in a department store basement floor,
but from a good place near my work.
The lady Kyeong-do's seeing.
Hello.
It's too cramped in here--
No. I was going to leave
after giving you this.
Are you busy?
No.
I wanted to get something from Málaga,
but I didn't find anything good.
Is that in Spain?
Yes.
Kyeong-do was very helpful.
Did things go well?
That is… kind of iffy.
I haven't received the answer yet.
Did Kyeong-do go to Spain?
I told you the other day.
-You must be anxious.
-I can't even sleep.
It must be very important.
Yes. This is my first project
since I joined the company.
I'm worried about it.
Gosh, even running a laundromat this size
is not easy.
A company that big must be even harder.
Oh, no...
I'm sorry. Excuse me…
Who keeps calling…
Lucas. Mother. Wait. Excuse me. Sorry.
Lucas?
Do you think he fell for that?
Did she leave?
But her bag is here.
Please excuse me…
Oh, my!
Excuse me, Father.
Yes… Yes, sure.
Lucas is coming. He's coming to JARIM!
-Lucas?
-It's a good thing, right?
This is totally awesome.
Being together with you two
brings me good luck. This is amazing!
Oh, my God. Let me call Kyeong-do.
Hey, Kyeong-do. This is crazy.
Don't be surprised.
Lucas is coming!
-Ouch…
-Oh, no.
I was so surprised.
I was more surprised
that you went to the laundromat.
That place has good energy.
I think that place is a lucky location.
Did you let the CEO know?
My sister is excited.
She's busy setting her schedule
to meet Lucas.
Our laundromat
is indeed a lucky location, but--
Things are turning out well
because I met you, Kyeong-do.
That's right. Here.
Speaking of which,
I need a painting of you as well.
No, just take that with you.
No, that should be here.
Since you have good energy,
I should have your portrait in my house.
Maybe about the size of…
a photograph?
-Why is mine small?
-It doesn't match my house design.
A small one next to my bed would be great.
Hey, my house also has a design.
You're on a lease.
But I live in my own house.
That's not logical.
Why are you nitpicking?
It is if I say it is.
Just finish your drink.
Is this what people call
an after-work drink?
-You kind of get fake drunk, right?
-No.
Imagine you do.
-Yes, I do.
-Right?
-Yes.
-Okay.
Gosh…
One more!
Sorry for calling you out so early.
Better than getting stopped out of nowhere
in front of my house.
It's nice and quiet.
Mr. Bae Jun-soo?
Min-woo got worked up and called me
when he got the notice.
You probably won't get
that 30 billion won back.
Director Seo Ji-woo is doing pretty well.
She scouted the lead designer of Pirco,
the company is hyped up.
We won't be selling the company.
Thanks to you, I could secure my credit.
If I had counted on Min-woo
and kept going…
I asked you to see me today
because I wanted to ask you
if you could invest the budget in us.
I'm going to meet Designer Lucas.
The key deal points are already agreed on.
I'll meet him to sign the contract.
Once Lucas arrives,
JARIM will change completely.
I'm sure you know it better than I do.
NAMU ART ACADEMY
Jeong-min, you're awesome.
Go wild, okay?
It's not a good look to babysit it.
As if this is nothing,
just ride it nonchalantly, okay?
You should've got a used one.
What if I scratch it?
I wouldn't let Actor Cha ride a used one.
Hey, if I get the delivery guy role,
I'd be the best.
You dream so small.
Ride with a pretty girl, not food--
-I can't ride with him every day.
-Honey.
Whatever. Forget it. I'm getting dizzy.
Try it. Ride it.
Wait. It's Hyeon-u. It's my boss.
CEO Im. Hello. How are you?
What? Really? Is he hurt badly?
That's a relief. Yes.
Yeah. I understudied it for quite long.
I can still recite it
at the drop of a hat.
Yes. Okay. Yup.
Yes. Goodbye. Yes, sir. Bye.
Why? Is someone hurt?
Waiting for Godot.
It's near the end of the run,
but the lead role is hurt.
Oh, no. Is it serious?
No, not that serious.
But you know,
I understudied the play twice.
-Yes.
-What's understudying?
You know, the replacement
when the actor can't make it.
Since you never know what might happen,
you memorize everything.
-Right, Woo-sik?
-Yes.
So…
He's telling me to take over
for the rest of the show.
Hey, you!
He told me to come now.
I'm in a hurry. Manager.
Okay. Where to? Where is it?
But I don't have a motorcycle license.
You idiot. Get off.
I do. I have a license.
Honey. You need to calm down.
Relax. Calm down!
Get ready for the class. I…
Let me go get ready for the play.
-For the play.
-Woo-sik, you're so hot.
-Go. Go now.
-Okay, I'll go now.
-Be careful. You've got this. Drive safe!
-Yes. Bye. I did it!
Is he riding that to work?
Does he even know how to get there?
Chinese food for lunch is too heavy. Jeez.
What did the food do wrong?
Perhaps it's your heart that's heavy?
I have no appetite.
I don't want to exercise either. Shit.
Well… Min-woo. You know, about last time,
what I said when I was drunk.
You know you must keep it a secret, right?
Hey, is that true though?
I can't tell if you got too drunk
and talked nonsense.
That makes no sense.
My father was Chairman Seo's best friend.
The old folks who run companies
tend to take each other's side.
Only my father knows about this.
One time, Chairman Seo got drunk
and cried his eyes out because of it.
But it's strange. Why did your family
accept someone like that?
Maybe because I have a lot of flaws,
damn it.
I used to do drugs and beat people.
I caused a lot of trouble.
Still, why would your father do that?
But Chairman Seo did adore her
like she was his own. I know that.
Min-woo, promise me
you must not tell anyone, okay?
Ji-yeon probably knows.
When I hint you the timing,
talk to her for me, will you?
I'm not interested in JARIM at all, okay?
It seems
Seo Ji-woo scored something in Spain.
Once this gets out,
how could she run the company?
She's not a real daughter.
So what are you going to do about it?
It's over. You might as well move on.
I need her back, you know?
If she grows old with that lowlife,
her life will become a real mess.
I'll get her back.
This mapo tofu is good.
GENETIC TESTS FOR TWO SISTERS
WHO SHARE THE SAME MOTHER
How am I supposed to test the DNA
with a dead man?
I can't open the coffin.
Damn it.
What's the point of having my portrait?
This is the best.
This…
Still, give it a try. You might find it.
Okay.
There's nothing… What's in here… Wait.
Whenever my sister was seeing someone,
she used to make paper cranes.
Every time she got a new boyfriend,
she made a thousand of them.
Would she still make them? She's 60 now.
Hey, are you going to put them in a jar
and give it to someone?
Do women still like it these days?
I've only given a jar
filled with rolled bills.
Origami is so old.
Mind your own businesses.
Why are you wasting paper?
You know, I've been only writing articles
about economy.
And now that I see something
so uneconomical and unproductive,
I'm getting a dopamine rush.
Didn't I do a good job?
That's pretty good.
Your sister taught you?
The flowers.
You were making these?
Be romantic and make the flowers.
Are you on an expedition to my team?
I wonder if our manager is back.
The chair…
What are you doing?
I've started a new hobby
using the lunch hour.
And you?
I'm trying it out
because it's interesting.
Okay.
I don't even have the energy
to make a fuss.
You're groundbreaking in so many ways,
Lee Kyeong-do.
The lunch hour is up.
-Let's get back to work.
-Yes.
Just out of curiosity,
-Are you going to put them in a nice jar?
-Yes.
Not just these little pieces of paper,
are you?
They're origami roses,
not pieces of paper.
Making them one by one
with heart and sincerity.
Hey, she can't even throw it out later.
It's useless.
Are you going to add something shiny too?
-Like what?
-What do you think, Doo-jin?
-A rose gold necklace?
-Bingo.
A diamond ring of a modest size?
Good.
Luxury brand earrings, bracelets,
et cetera.
-Thank you.
-Shallow.
-What…
-Excuse me?
I'd welcome these origami roses
made with such care for me.
Is that so? Then make them with him
in the meeting room every day at lunch.
I don't like to make them myself.
Here, Assistant Manager.
Yes.
Thank you.
Hey, lunch time's up,
let's get back to work.
Work now.
Hobbies are for lunchtime.
Not just these little pieces of paper,
are you?
Jeez. Damn it.
Is this a lucky draw or what?
Making them one by one
with heart and sincerity.
Hey, she can't even throw it out later.
It's useless.
Are you going to add something shiny too?
Forget it. Gosh. Jeez.
Jeez.
WAITING FOR GODOT
CHA WOO-SIK
Dong-won. Go stand there.
Hey, Woo-sik gets to perform
by chance, right?
What do you mean "by chance"? A prepared
actor is getting his moment to shine.
The original actor got hurt--
You need to talk less.
Dong-won, isn't your dad cool?
Yes, he's cool.
-All right. Let's go.
-He's handsome.
Didn't you play the Boy in this play?
You didn't even come to watch.
"Godot is not coming.
Ji-woo is not coming."
How many times did you watch this play?
Only when you wrote that article?
Sometimes at the national theater
whenever it came to my mind.
This stop is the national theater.
WAITING FOR GODOT
The next stop
is Songjeong Integrated Center.
NATIONAL THEATER
WAITING FOR GODOT
Sorry.
HAEUM THEATER
Hurry up.
WAITING FOR GODOT
HAEUM NATIONAL THEATER
JANGCHUNG SNACK BAR
WAITING FOR GODOT
FINAL PERFORMANCE
Waiting for Godot?
Yes, it's been performed every year,
but this year will be the last one.
Why should we write about this?
They were in deficit due to low turnout,
yet the play ran for ten years.
But now, they can't keep going anymore,
so it'll be their last show.
It's meaningful. A theater that put on
a good play despite no profit.
I thought it'd be a good article.
Kyeong-do will write
about Godot?
What does that smile mean?
I remembered someone else
also saying Godot sounded like Kyeong-do.
-It's personal, isn't it?
-No.
It is.
Sure, go with it.
It better be good.
Yup. I'll do my best.
Thank you.
You've been showing it
despite the long deficit.
What kept you going?
It's not that I endured it
because I had any specific reason.
"Just for this year. Just one more year."
Then it's been ten years.
It seems the cast didn't change much
over the decade. Am I right?
That's part of it.
After the show ends,
we get some soju and go home.
Then the next year, we gather again.
Preparing Godot was…
How can I put it?
It's not something you do out of duty,
but something you're doing
before you even realize. Is that it?
When the article is out, buy the paper.
And keep it. It's our history.
Godot.
I see. Then are you ending it too?
Ending what?
Waiting For Godot is closing.
Are you moving on as well?
Honey. That sounds like
he couldn't go on a date because of her.
Read the room.
Why bother? That's not like you.
Right. Move on, will you?
She disappeared without a trace.
If you know where she is,
you'd at least visit her.
For goodness' sake,
move on already, will you?
I already have.
Okay, let's call it that.
-Here.
-No, I mean it.
Now, Waiting for Godot is over.
Everything is over.
Everyone, raise your glasses. Cheers.
-Cheers.
-Sure, cheers.
Cheers.
We've come a long way.
Is it finally over tomorrow?
You must be getting tired.
It's not that I'm tired.
I've simply been walking forward.
I don't know what I passed
or what passed me.
Everything
sounds like an old song.
The lyrics are gone, but the melody keeps
ringing in my mouth. A song like that.
I don't even know if I sang it
or if someone else sang it.
I don't know anymore.
WAITING FOR GODOT
HAEUM NATIONAL THEATER
-Mr. Kim.
-Yes?
Do you like this play that much?
You watch it every time you come to Korea.
Is it still fun?
It's boring.
Hurry up. We're late.
WAITING FOR GODOT
What a liar.
He said he'd come if I waited.
WAITING FOR GODOT
Oh… So hot.
Why do you never see him
even though you come every year?
But you watch that damn play every time.
I just watch it for old times' sake.
We had so much fun then.
Ji-woo.
Are you really not going to see Kyeong-do?
Se-yeong, you see…
I thought it was wrong after our breakup
so I went to see him.
He wanted to buy me a pork cutlet,
so I was going to ask him to buy it.
While sitting in that restaurant,
I was going to call Kyeong-do.
And an older couple
were having the pork cutlet next to me.
It must've been her birthday.
The man bought her a 50,000-won blouse.
And the woman nagged at him
for buying something so expensive.
She seemed to like it though.
What are you talking about
all of a sudden?
They were Kyeong-do's parents.
What?
They were talking to him on the phone.
That's when I understood
what Kyeong-do meant.
There is a life I'm not aware of.
And I'll never know.
Every time that happens,
I'll hurt Kyeong-do's feelings.
Then we'll end up
hurting each other again.
WAITING FOR GODOT
THE LAST SHOW
The curtain's closed.
I should end it as well.
With my idiot Kyeong-do.
Every time I watch it,
I think it's long and hard to understand.
I still can't believe you watched it
so many times.
Hey, then can you tell
what social absurdity is
just by looking at it?
But how come
we've never run into each other?
Maybe one of us is lying.
Then you're lying.
I even wrote an article about it.
I'm not lying either.
What?
Godot, you, and me,
we must have missed each other so fiercely
to end up here now.
I got something for you.
I wanted to ask you.
I always wanted to ask you if you had it.
Why didn't you?
Because you'd be in pain,
and so would I.
Don't leave me now.
Or I'll die.
Triple the dosage.
Drink it while it's warm.
This medicine is kind of bitter.
This is your favorite chocolate.
I went to buy some myself this morning.
I'll drink it later.
It's only effective when it's warm.
Come on, don't be like Ro-a.
Even if it's bitter,
endure it and drink it up.
I used good deer antlers.
LEE GANG-HYEON
Oh, my. Oh, no.
Is your hand okay?
Yes, I'm okay. Honey. Sorry.
Okay.
Yes, Executive Lee.
Yes.
Hello.
DONGWOON DAILY
LEE KYEONG-DO
Can you check if there's a graduate
named Yoo Dan-bi?
We can't provide personal information
at our discretion.
Then,
can you just check
if she graduated from here?
That is--
I'm not trying to
write an article about it. Please?
What year did she enter?
EDUCATION
ENROLLMENT PERIOD
Here.
There is no graduate named Yoo Dan-bi.
Do I report to you from now on?
Yes.
Is the pork cutlet good?
Yes. Do you want a piece?
Yes.
Everything is tasty here.
Bae Jun-soo went to the US.
And he stopped meeting Kang Min-woo.
The M&A expert investor.
Is he in Manhattan?
I think so.
Should I go?
Why bother going that far?
Follow this person, from where she lives
to what she does after work.
YOO DAN-BI
Watch all her followers
and every story she posts.
Okay.
Is the gimbap good?
Yes.
Teacher,
I'm okay
with the integral calculus questions,
but I'm stuck with geometry.
Really?
I marked them. I got everything right.
You're at an academy, aren't you?
I have English after math.
Then you need to move
to the other class, right?
Yes.
My workbooks.
Okay.
Here.
-Do you want to go to the class?
-Okay.
Oh, wait.
Secretary Cha,
can you grab the report from my room?
Don't send Secretary Yoo.
It's confidential.
Bye.
All right.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Come on.
My English teacher…
Why would they...
I'm here to meet CEO Seo Ji-yeon.
One second.
Mr. Lee Kyeong-do is here to meet the CEO.
Yes, okay.
-At two o'clock, right?
-Yes.
The CEO isn't available at the moment.
Can you wait a moment?
Oh, okay. Sure.
This isn't the classroom.
It's right around the corner.
Go on. Let's go. Come.
Isn't that Ms. Seo?
Let me help you.
Don't you steal mine…
Ji-yeon. What's wrong?
Please be seated.
Waiting for Godot will start soon.
Sorry.
WAITING FOR GODOT
Hurry up.
JANGCHUNG SNACK BAR
When I went to meet you at the airport,
I was thinking,
Only if you don't leave.
Was I the only immature kid?
Seo Ji-yeon's dementia,
Seo Ji-woo being an illegitimate child...
Where that asshole is going,
I have to be there first.
If Ji-woo really puts her mind to it,
even ten guys couldn't take her down.
An illegitimate child out of wedlock.
It's a nice keyword.
Let's get ahead of him.
You did earn the assistant manager title.
Just show yourself.
Just as I am.